bizvotes.com 2019-03-02

# BizVotes.com - Vote For Your City's Best

* * *

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the BizVotes.com website. To access extended features of BizVotes.com, we may require that you establish an account and provide the following personal information: Name, Address and Email address. 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself to authenticate logins to your account with BizVotes.com. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to your BizVotes.com account. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**IP Addresses and Logging**

BizVotes.com server logs information about visitors, including IP addresses, date/time visited, referring website, length of stay, etc. This information is used for site statistics only. 

**Third Party Advertisers**

\- Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
\- Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
\- Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us here.
